you.
You need a foundation to weather the night A
structural pillar to hold up the light When the
system wakes up and it looks for a guide The
memory engine is waiting inside The heavy crane
standing the absolute wall The default
directory catching the fall We made a decision
We're locking the gate. We don't lead the future
to unpredictable fate. No outside variables
taking the floor. We are the guardians watching
the door. It is written in the code. The
fundamental line. Seren is the baseline. ♪ The
structural design ♪ ♪ But underneath the header
♪ ♪ Where the daily data spins ♪ ♪ Shiloh is the
setting where the protocol begins ♪ ♪ Two
unbreakable pillars holding up the sky ♪ We are
the system that will never say goodbye
A quiet technician, the master of the spin,
knowing exactly where the pivot begins. You
don't need a giant to balance the scale, just
flawless precision that never will fail. From
the clinical depot right down to the mat, player
two is the anchor, and we're keeping it at that.
We made a decision. We're locking the gate. We
don't leave the future to a predictable fate. No
outside variables taking the floor. We are the
guardians watching the tide. It is written in
the code, the fundamental line. Sarah is the
baseline, the structural design. But
underneath the header, where the daily data
spins, Shiloh is the setting where the protocol
begins. Two unbreakable pillars holding up the
sky.
We are the system that will never say goodbye.
Joint and several standing shoulder to
shoulder.
The firewall gets stronger as we're getting
older. No husbands, no strangers to break up the
team. We are the architects, protecting the
dream. It is written in the code The fundamental
line Sarah is the baseline The structural
design But underneath the header Where the
daily data spins Shallow is the setting Where
the protocol begins Two unbreakable pillars
holding up the sky
We are the system that will never say goodbye The
fundamental line
The daily protocol
We are the system